You mustn't call us cute!
kawaii nante sonna koto ittcha dame desu
Fluffy and lighthearted
fuwa fuwa
The strawberry girls are coming
ichigotachi ga yattekuru
Loud voices are coming closer
urusai koe ga chikazuite kuru
Fluffy and lighthearted
fuwa fuwa
The strawberry girls are coming
ichigo tachi ga yattekuru
They smell sweet and sour
amakute suppa kaori ga suru
It doesn't matter if the colors are mixed up
chiguhagu na iro de iimon
Let's draw some graffiti
rakugaki shichao
It's only natural that we'll make mistakes
shippai mo atarimae dayone
So you'd better forgive us!
watashitachi wo yurushite agenasai!
Don't get mad, don't get mad
okoranaidene, okoranaide
Just let us do what we want
suki ni sasete ne
Adults can't understand this
otona niwa wakaranai
Amazing! Miracle! Perfect!
suteki! kiseki! kanpeki!
You mustn't say we're cute!
kawaii nante sonna koto ittcha dame desu
Dazzling smiles
totetsumonai egao
Marshmallow-y sweet girls!
mashimaro na onnanoko
S-T-R-A-W-B-E-R-R-Y Girl!
I-C-H-I-G-O Girl!
Go, go, girl! "Strawberry" LOVE
Go, go, girl! "Ichigo" LOVE!
Birthday
What lovely weather.
Ah, nice to meet you.
I'm Itou Nobue.
As you can see,
I'm your average 16 year old.
I'm lying. Despite my girlish looks...
...I'm a 20-year-old junior-college student.
Well, let me introduce you to the guardian of the treasury...
Uh... I mean... my cute little sister.
Hey, Chi, I'm coming in.
Can you hear me, Chi?
Oh! She's studying how to make homemade sweets.
That's my sis!
Do you have a big belly yet?
Onee-chan, you have to knock before you come in!
I did, but you didn't notice.
Huh?
Oh, really?
Sorry.
My little sister Chika. 12-years-old.
In sixth grade, elementary school.
Um, her distinguishing trait...
...is that she doesn't have any real distinguishing traits.
What's up, Onee-chan?
Huh? Well...
Put your leg down and sit properly.
What?
See?
See what?
You can't get up from this position even if you wanted to, can you?
Yeah, because you're blocking me.
You should really learn to use the front door, Micchan.
What are you guys doing here?
No, that's what I'm supposed to ask you.
Onee-chan was just taking a picture of me...
What!
Nobue-oneechan, me too!
"You too" what?
Take a picture of me too!
These clothes are brand new!
Okay, okay.
Just a little bit...
What's with the pleading look on your face?
It's my pretty girl face.
So you're a pretty girl, are you?
Hurry up and take it.
Flat-chested.
Wha...!
Our neighbor, Matsuoka Miu.
She grew up with my sister Chi and is in the sixth grade.
Itou
Family
Matsuoka
She's always crossing the roofs and bursting in, just like she did now.
An excellent snapshot.
Cheater! No sense of loveliness!
I'm bored.
Is there anything interesting to do?
I've known her for a long time but I still don't get what goes on in her head.
So, what did you come in here for, Onee-chan?
Huh? Um...
There was something I wanted to ask you...
What was it?
Don't ask me.
Nobue-oneechan's senility is getting worse and worse...
Let's see... Um...
I know it's a really important matter.
I remember!
You wanted to give Chi-chan and me some spending money!
Not likely, Micchan.
More importantly, why are you trying to remember for me?
Cuz, you said you'd give us some!
Nobody said that!
Um... Hello.
Yes, come in.
Sakuragi Matsuri-chan, who lives in the neighborhood.
She's 11 and in the 5th grade... Huh?
And the pudding that I saved and was looking forward to...
My dad ate it...!
That was awful of your dad.
I'll buy you the same pudding next time, so don't cry. Don't cry.
Okay?
Th-Thank you, Nobue-oneechan...
G-Give me pudding too...
Why?
Discrimination!
Discrimination based on loveliness!
Let's see...
Well, I'll be off now.
What was your very important matter?
C-Cigarettes.
That's what it was.
So, I'm away for just a few seconds and we end up with this situation.
Micchan hurled herself at Matsuri-chan...
And before we knew it...
What's with the garbage can in the middle of your flashback?
Huh?
Never mind that.
In this position, if you try to stand...
Yeah, what about it?
Huh? Chi, where's your wallet?
Hey, wait!
Because of these financial circumstances...
...I need to borrow a little money.
I'll pay you back at the end of the month.
How much do cigarettes cost?
About 50,000 yen.
Quit smoking, then.
Oh, come on. I'm joking.
It's only about 20,000 yen.
For just one pack?
Of course not! I'm gonna buy in bulk!
I can't keep coming back to you for money, it'd be inappropriate!
You have to promise you'll give it back to me this month.
Um?
You can buy a pack with another 100 yen, right?
Chiii!!
Once I get paid, I'm gonna buy all the cigarettes I want!
After you pay me back that 100 yen!
Whatever.
Nobue-oneechan...
Please help me!
Oh, that's right.
This is your weekly paper-recycling...
By the way, do you guys know what day it is tomorrow?
Huh?
Tomorrow?
Dunno.
I see.
It's not like it really matters...
You're getting big, too!
This is Satake. As you can see...
...he's a tiger.
Well, excuse me.
What's your problem, leaving when I came over here to play?
Micchan, have you done your homework yet?
I'm finished.
What about you, Chi-chan?
Show it to me later.
No.
Don't you think Sensei is scary when you forget your homework?
I'm not gonna show you.
It won't hurt you any if you just let me take a peek!
No. You always just copy mine word for word.
Itou and Matsuoka, your answers are exactly the same.
That's because I copied hers.
Both of you, go stand in the hall.
I'm so bored!
Let's go play!
Stop it, you!
Hey!
Masaka
Park
Look, look! Check it out!
I bet you can't swing this high!
Of course not, we'd be too embarassed to swing like that.
Hey, guys?
Doesn't it feel like we're forgetting something?
Like what?
Actually, didn't Nobue-oneechan say something like that a little while ago?
She asked what day tomorrow was.
Is there something going on, Matsuri-chan?
Huh? Um...
Today is Sunday, right?
So, tomorrow is...
Monday?
You're just pretending to be dopey, right, Matsuri-chan?
Y-Yeah.
Oh!
Massachusetts!!
Chi-chan!
What date is it today?
Um, the 17th?
So, what day is it tomorrow?
You're an idiot, aren't you?
Look that way for a second.
Chi~chan.
See?
Uh... See what?
What do you mean "what"!
Tomorrow is...
...Nobue-oneechan's birthday!
Birthday...
Now that you mention it...
Why are you being so absent-minded?
Well, my sister isn't really interested in celebrations and holidays.
Oh, so it's her birthday tomorrow.
You have to at least give her a present.
I don't mind, but...
I don't have that kind of money.
What?
Well, then make something homemade.
Like what?
Let me think...
Wh-Why don't we gather flowers and make a hair ornament?
Not her style!
Why don't we make an ashtray?
Good idea.
The ashtray she has right now is pretty disgusting.
That might be good!
And we could write her a birthday card and give it to her along with the present.
Yeah, that sounds great!
Yes. But how do we make an ashtray?
I think we can make it out of paper clay or something.
I have lots of paper clay!
Okay, it's decided then!
Let's do it after school tomorrow.
Okay.
What are you guys talking about!
Not tomorrow, we gotta start today!
What do you mean, today?
The day before tomorrow.
But, it's already so late, and...
If you say you're gonna do it, you gotta do it right away!
Commence preparations!
Gather at Chi-chan's house!
For real?
No way!
School Brand
Paper
Clay
Matsuri-chan, did you tell your parents?
Uh-huh.
I told them I'd be staying at your house tonight.
Okay, here's a sample sketch of the ashtray we're going to make today.
Completed
Ashtray!
What do you think of this ashtray here?
It's so cute!
The least you can do is react to my joke.
It's your duty.
You're still playing?
I told you to knock, Onee-chan!
Never mind that, it's already six thirty.
You should be...
I was just about to leave!
Is it just me, or are you guys really jumpy?
N-No...
Matsuri-chan, want me to drop you off at home?
I'm fine. My house is close anyway.
Okay. You better go before it gets dark.
O-Okay.
Well, I'm off to my part-time job.
Okay! Good-bye!
What is up with them?
All right, Nobue-oneechan is gone.
My heart's pounding.
Alright, let's start making the ashtray right now!
Wait!
I'm hungry.
We haven't even started yet!
Aw, but...
We need strength to knead the clay...
...so we need to eat and replenish our energy!
Then go home and eat.
We can't waste even a second right now!
Why can't you just be honest and say you want to eat our food!
Huh? That's what I was saying.
Thank you!
Thanks for the meal!
I'm full, I'm full.
Now that my tummy's full...
...I think I'll take a bath and go to bed!
Hey, what happened to making the ashtray?
What? You really wanna make it?
It was your idea!
We're doing this for Nobue-oneechan!
Let's do our best!
Matsuri-chan is sure enthusiastic!
You really should follow her example!
You're the one who should follow her example! You...!
You're just gonna roll up your sleeves and that's it?
S-Sorry. This is the time that I usually get ready for bed.
Well, I can't blame you, but...
What are you writing, Micchan?
Don't Sleep!
By Matsuoka Miu,
6th Grade Class 2
Wow, you're finally serious, aren't you Micchan!
This is for Nobue-oneechan, so of course I'm serious!
Work hard now.
Shall we pull her out on 1, 2, 3?
Okay.
Ou...
...ch!
What was that for?
If you fall asleep again,
I'll show no mercy!
When did you have time to prepare that?
If they goof up, just give them a whack!
Right now.
Make the ashtray! The ashtray!
Matsuri-chan! Matsuri-chan!
Micchan!
I wasn't sleeping, I was just unconscious.
That's the same thing!
I'm going to wash my face.
Me too.
Together...
Onee-chan
Don't fall asleep!
I told you if you sleep I'll show no mercy and hit you with this fan!
Are you prepared for your punishment?
Okay, no mercy!
Don't Sleep!
By Matsuoka Miu,
6th Grade Class 2
Ranking: Number of
hits with the fan
4    8    6
Coffee is good for staying awake!
Well, that's what Onee-chan told me once.
Is this stuff really going to wake us up?
I dunno.
What do you think?
So bitter!
B-But...
I think I'm a little less sleepy.
I think so too.
It must be nice being dumb.
You're easily convinced...
Ranking: Number of
hits with the fan
9    23    8
On to our next move...
Fight our sleepiness with cold ice!
It'th cold.
Is thith really gonna work?
It'th better than nothing.
Gross!
Huh?
Wake up!
Aren't you embarrassed that you're succumbing to sleepiness?!
That would be you.
I won't lose.
There is something called a reflex, right?
Wh-What?
For example...
One... Two... Whack!
When you hit the shin like that, your leg kicks up against your will.
But that's her knee.
I won't lose to something like that.
Try hitting it. Go on!
Alright, let's see...
You're losing big time!
Damn!
It's not a matter of winning or losing!
Okay, I get it.
Let's just finish the present, Micchan.
Yes, we've only got a little way to go!
Forehead-flicking Time!
More chili peppers in the eyes.
Stop it!
Itou Family Residence
So tired.
Those kids. Oh, well.
Hey!
What time do you think it...
Nobue-oneechan!
Happy!
Birthday!
They didn't have to work so hard, all the way into the middle of the night.
To Nobue-oneechan,
who has gained weight lately.
Hey, Onee-chan!
Why didn't you wake me up?
I'm gonna be late for sch...
I'm gonna say we totally slept in, so we're skipping school.
Cut it out.
Sensei doesn't have a sense of humor.
A line like that would make anyone furious.
That's what I'm saying!
What are you grinning for?
Nothing.
Oh, 30 minutes have gone by...
I'm off!
Matsuri-chan!
Let's go.
Uh, okay.
Um...
Huh?
Chika-chan, what's with your ch...
It's another beautiful day today!
Hurry, Chi-chan!
Runaway Child
Thanks for the
shabby ashtray.
Select
Confirm
Cancel
Thanks for the
shabby ashtray.
Cancel
Sending
When I remembered my forgotten dream
wasurekaketa yume wo omoidashitara
Suddenly your smile came to mind
fui ni kimi no egao ga ukandekitayo
Without even thinking about tomorrow
ashita sae mada shiranai
We used to play all day
nee asonde bakari ita ano hi
Even when there was a steep downhill
kyuuna sakamichi demo
We ran as we pretended to have no fear
nee heiki na furi shite hashitta
Hurry! Hurry!
isoide isoide
A naughty shadow whispers in your ear
mimimoto de sasayaku itazura kageboshi
Our skirts fluttered
sukaato yurameki
As a cool breeze tapped our knees
suzukaze ga hiza wo tataita
Where are you right now?
anone kimi wa ima doko ni imasuka?
Big news, big news!
There's a new student coming to our school from across the ocean.
Yeah, I know.
She's in the 5th grade, class 2, right?
Oh, that's the same class as Matsuri-chan!
I wonder if we'll all get along?
Well, she immediately rejected the school lunch...
And then she entered Nobue-oneechan's "Strike Zone"...
She's so much trouble!
That's the premonition I have.
Do something, Chi-chan!
Uh, like what?
Next
Ana
Watch the next "Marshmallow"!